<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Legal terms on Kubirds</title><link>https://kubirds.com/legals/</link><description>Recent content in Legal terms on Kubirds</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubirds.com/legals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Company</title><link>https://kubirds.com/legals/company/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubirds.com/legals/company/</guid><description>Identification Corporate Name Link Society Legal Form SAS Share Capital 3€ Address 3rd Saint Lugles Street, Lillers 62190, France Website https://link-society.com (fr) Phone Number (+33) 07 82 16 83 10 E-Mail contact@link-society.com Host Corporate Name Github, Inc. Legal Form Subsidiary Address San Francisco, California, USA</description></item><item><title>Terms of service</title><link>https://kubirds.com/legals/terms-of-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubirds.com/legals/terms-of-service/</guid><description>Website Terms and Conditions of Use 1. Terms By accessing this Website, accessible from https://kubirds.com, you are agreeing to be bound by these Website Terms and Conditions of Use and agree that you are responsible for the agreement with any applicable local laws. If you disagree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from accessing this site. The materials contained in this Website are protected by copyright and trade mark law.</description></item><item><title>Privacy policy</title><link>https://kubirds.com/legals/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubirds.com/legals/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy for Link-Society At kubirds.com, accessible from https://kubirds.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by kubirds.com and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) We are a Data Controller of your information.</description></item></channel></rss>